# MARVIN JOHN AGBUYA

FRONT END DEVELOPER





**EMAIL** marvinjohnagbuya@gmail.com



LINKEDIN linkedin.com/in/marvinja

Developer and Designer specialising in fields such as UX/UI, Front End Web Development and Game Design. I've worked as a Microsite Developer at Serviceseeking.com for 7 months, an Assistant Administrator at Hajos, Anstee & Associates for 1 year and I have been working as a Website Administrator at ICMS Australasia for over 2 years.

## **SKILLS**

<u>HTML5 CSS Javascript Sass Bootstrap p5.js Git Jekyll Gatsby.js JSON</u> <u>PHP Node.js</u>

<u>UX Design</u> <u>Web Design</u> <u>Game Design</u> <u>Wireframing</u> <u>Accessibility</u>

Microsoft Office Affinity Designer Affinity Publisher Affinity Photo Mailchimp

# **EDUCATION**

2013 - 15

#### **BACHELOR OF DESIGN COMPUTING**

University of Sydney

2016 - 17

ADV. DIPL. OF PROF. GAME DEV. - GAME DESIGN & PRODUCTION

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

# **REFERENCES**

Contact details available on request

Web Master

**BLAIR HARDAKER** 

ICMS Australasia Pty Ltd

Senior Event Manager

**EMMA CHALMERS** 

ICMS Australasia Pty Ltd

# MARVIN JOHN AGBUYA

FRONT END DEVELOPER





**EMAIL** marvinjohnagbuya@gmail.com



LINKEDIN linkedin.com/in/marvinja

## **EXPERIENCE**

2018 - CURRENT

#### **WEBSITE ADMINISTRATOR**

ICMS Australasia Pty Ltd

#### **Responsiblities:**

- Created and designed websites for conferences from briefs given by clients
- Used HTML5, Sass, CSS, PHP and Bootstrap, Javascript, Jekyll, Gatsby.js to create websites and emails
- Updated websites and created new features such as: Event Programs, Speaker Biography Modals, Image Galleries, etc.
- Create emails on Mailchimp for each conference
- Corresponding with Event Managers
- Use Affinity Designer/Photo to edit images to be suitable for the web

2017 - 18

#### **ASSISTANT ADMINISTRATOR**

Hajos Anstee & Associates

#### **Responsiblities:**

- Created manila folders for new clients
- File organisation
- Digitisation of Corporate Registers
- External client organisation
- Data Entry

2013 - 14

#### MICROWEBSITE DEVELOPER

Service Seeking Pty Ltd

#### **Responsiblities:**

- Edited HTML, CSS, Javascript files to create microsites.
- Attached Google Analytics to the microsites
- Updated main website with links to the microsites.

# MARVIN JOHN AGBUYA

FRONT END DEVELOPER





**EMAIL** marvinjohnagbuya@gmail.com



LINKEDIN linkedin.com/in/marvinja

# VOLUNTEERING

2016

### **QA TESTER**

**Epiphany Games Pty Ltd** 

#### **Responsiblities:**

- Tested games for bugs
- Discovered how the bugs occurred and how to reproduce them
- Reported Bugs using JIRA

2013 - 16

#### **GENERAL EXECUTIVE AND DANCE TEACHER**

Soulxpress Hip Hip Society

### Responsiblities:

- Taught hip hop/urban choreography classes
- Organised and choreographed performances for events
- Helped other executives with tasks to help organise events and gatherings